http://www.aurelia-art.com/index.php/en/privacy-policy

Personalized Commissions
All the info about personalized drawing commissions can be found HERE. If you have any questions, contact me.
Information
Terms of ServicePrivacy Policy
Galleries
Originals for PurchaseCommissionsJensen AcklesDonnie Wahlberg / NKOTBThe Lord of the RingsStar WarsStargateCinemaTelevisionMusicNatureMiscellaneous (Portraits & more)FantasyArts and CraftAutographs
Tutorials Menu
Anatomy of a DrawingDrawing Hair: Leia OrganaDrawing Hair: Amanda TappingHow to draw an eye
Related links
Society6 storeInprnt storeFacebook: Artist PageFacebook: Personal AccountTwitter AccountInstagramDeviantArt PageTumblr
By using this online website, you consent to the use of Cookies. More info here
Privacy Policy
Here is the Privacy Policy for Aurelia-art.com
About the site and the firm
Personal data
Items purchased at Aurelia-art.com
Tax and customs charges
Links to other sites
IP address and cookies
Amazon Associates Programs
Changes to the privacy policy
About the site and the firm
The site “Art by/par Aurelia” and the firm “Aurelia-art.com” belong to Aurélia Chaintreuil, currently residing in Charentay (69220), France.
The firm is registered at Chambre des Métiers et de l’Artisanat du Rhône.Aurelia-art.com18 Allée des LibellulesLieu-dit Delphingue69220 CHARENTAY, FrancePhone: +33 6 13 22 17 03 (in French only)SIRET: 507 629 038 00013By virtue of its “micro firm” status (French term: micro entreprise), aurelia-art.com works under VAT exemption which means VAT is not applicable, article 293 B of French general tax code.
The site “Art by/par Aurelia” is hosted by www.siteground.comSiteGround Spain S.L.Calle Prim 1928004 Madrid, Spain
Back to "Privacy Policy" menu
Personal data
To order at Aurelia-art.com, you don't need an account on the site. You only need a valid email address to process the order and for a possible Paypal invoice in case you choose this method of payment. Know that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. Therefore, despite all the efforts expended to use reliable means to protect your personal information, I cannot guarantee an absolute security. I assume no liability for any disclosure of data due to errors in transmission, unauthorized third party access or other acts of third parties. I cannot be responsible for acts or omissions I cannot control.
Please be aware that no bank data is recorded on the site, the payments being done on the site of Paypal (secured site).
In accordance with article 26 of French law “Informatique et libertés” (Information technology and liberties), the user is informed that the nominative data collected within the framework of service are necessary for its good functioning. The user has a right of access, of modification, of removal and of opposition to the transfer of his data. So you can modify your data at any time.
I am committed to protecting your privacy. Under no circumstances do I rent, trade or share your e-mail address with any other company for marketing purposes without your consent. The personal information you provide me are used only for processing your order, keeping you informed of its advancement and contacting you if I have problems processing it.
Back to "Privacy Policy" menu
Items purchased at Aurelia-art.com
If you have questions relating to purchases such as prices, shipping conditions, returns policy, etc…, please check the FAQ or the Terms of Service.
All the prices displayed in the print shop are in euros. If you want to know the value of your transaction in your own currency, you can use a currency converter such as www.xe.com. I cannot guarantee the reliability of the information provided by the converter.
Back to "Privacy Policy" menu
Tax and customs charges
The prices displayed on aurelia-art.com include all the taxes. Orders outside the EU may be subject to local taxes, import duties or customs charges. For further information, please contact your local customs office. Please also be aware that cross-border shipments may be subject to opening and inspection by customs authorities.
Back to "Privacy Policy" menu
Links to other sites
This website contains links to other sites. Please be aware that aurelia-art.com is not responsible for the privacy practices of these other websites. So I encourage you to be vigilant when you leave this site and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information.
Back to "Privacy Policy" menu
IP address and cookies
We also collect non-personal information from you, such as your browser type, the URL of the previous website you’ve just visited, your ISP (Internet service provider), your operating system, and your IP address. This non-personal information cannot be used to easily identify you. They are used to gather broad demographic information and to recognize customer traffic patterns and site usage. This information helps us in developing the design and layout of the site.
In addition, like almost all websites, aurelia-art.com uses cookies. If you haven’t changed your computer’s settings, most likely your browser already accepts cookies. Cookies are bits of information that are stored on your computer by your web browser. Although cookies don’t store any of your personal information, they allow to provide you with a more personalized user experience.
Back to "Privacy Policy" menu
Amazon Associates Programs
Aurelia-art.com is a participant in different Amazon Associates Programs and I have to clearly state it on my website.So here is what you should now: Aurelia-art.com is a participant in the Amazon Europe S.A.R.L. Associates Programme, an affiliate advertising program designed to provide a means for sites to earn advertising fees by advertising and linking to amazon.fr and amazon.co.uk.
Back to "Privacy Policy" menu
Changes to the privacy policy
If I decide to change a part or the whole privacy policy, I’ll let you know by posting an announcement on the home page of the website. These changes will become effective at the given date. The new policy will apply to all current and past users of the website and will replace any prior policies that are inconsistent with it.
Privacy Policy Effective Date: May 2020
If you have any questions concerning the privacy policy of aurelia-art.com, please contact me by email.
Back to "Privacy Policy" menu
FaLang translation system by Faboba
Close info
Additional information
Work in Progress
Don't miss any WIP update:Twitter ; Facebook ; Instagram
Society6 Store
Interested in derivative products of my drawings? Check out my Society6 store.(More info, see FAQ)
About Art by Aurélia
Welcome to Art by Aurelia, a gallery exposing, among other creations, celebrity portraits and fan arts. Aurelia-art.com offers you 3 kind of products: HQ prints of the original creations exposed in the galleries, originals of these drawings when they are available and personalized drawing commissions.Since the new drawings are being shown as works in progress, I hope you'll come by often to check for updates.
Drawing requests
Considering the number of hours needed to make a portrait, I don't take requests (i.e. requests for a free drawing).If, on the other hand, you want to order a drawing, use the contact form. Thanks for your understanding.
Amazon Associates
Support this website by visiting the Amazon webstores:Amazon.frAmazon.co.uk
Link Me
Link to Art by Aurelia - Drawing Portraits using one of the buttons below. Please host it on your own server. Thanks!
More...
